(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T22:34:54.769235",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
わっふぁー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Waha! We're zombies, zombies
「死にたい死にたい」って死んでるじゃん
"Wanna die, wanna die," but you're already dead
なのに「会いたい会いたい」が消えないじゃん
Even still, "I miss you, I miss you" just won't disappear
いつだって痛いの痛いの飛んでいかないの
All the pain, all the pain, it won't go away
なんでなんで
Why, tell me, why
寂しさだけ残っちゃってるんだ
The only thing remaining is my loneliness
わっふぁー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Waha! We're zombies, zombies
傷を縫って 蜜を塗って
Stitch the wounds, apply the honey
何度だって 恋をするコーデ
Over and over, love is sure to be there
傷を擦って 蜜を吸って
Rub the wounds, suck the honey
何度だって 恋がしたい
Over and over, I want to fall in love
あたしなっちゃってるの
I'm turning into...
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
腐りかけもいいね いいね
Even if I'm half-decomposed, it's not bad!
きみもなっちゃえば？
Why don't you do it too?
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
ふたりだけの シークレット シークレット
Between you and me, a secret!
わっふぁー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Waha! We're zombies, zombies
ドッキドキが もう聞こえない
My beating heart, I can't hear it anymore
わっふぁー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Waha! We're zombies, zombies
ぎゅっとしても 冷たいまま
Your body is cold even when we hug
なっちゃったんじゃ しょうがないね
Well, if we transform, it's fine!
わっふぁー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Waha! We're zombies, zombies
もう撫でられても 痒くないよ 痒くないよ
Now, even if you touch me, it doesn't itch
もう噛み付いても 美味しくないよ 美味しくないよ
Now, even if you bite me, it's not yummy
嫉妬吐き出しちゃう ジャックポット
Spitting out jealousy, the jackpot
縫い目は デマ それ以上覗かないで
The stitches are fake, please don't look any closer
傷を縫って 蜜を塗って
Stitch the wounds, apply the honey
何度だって 恋をするコーデ
Over and over, love is sure to be there
傷を擦って 蜜を吸って
Rub the wounds, suck the honey
何度だって 恋がしたい
Over and over, I want to fall in love
ふたりなっちゃえば
If we both transform
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
死なないから いいじゃん いいじゃん
It's fine since we will never die!
愛し合っちゃえば
If we just love each other
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
きみ以外はないね ないね
You're the only one for me!
あたしなっちゃってるの
I'm turning into...
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
腐りかけもいいね いいね
Even if I'm half-decomposed, it's not bad!
きみもなっちゃえば？
Why don't you do it too?
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
ふたりだけの シークレット
Between you and me, a secret!
ふたりなっちゃえば
If we both transform
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
死なないから いいじゃん いいじゃん
It's fine since we will never die!
愛し合っちゃえば
If we just love each other
あいらびゅー あいらびゅー
I love you, I love you
きみ以外はないね ないね
You're the only one for me!
わっふぁー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Waha! We're zombies, zombies
ドッキドキが もう聞こえない
My beating heart, I can't hear it anymore
わっふぁー We’re ゾンビゾンビ
Waha! We're zombies, zombies
ぎゅっとしても 冷たいまま
Your body is cold even when we hug
なっちゃったんじゃ しょうがないね
Well, if we transform, it's fine!
「死にたい死にたい」って死んでるじゃん
"Wanna die, wanna die," but you're already dead
なのに「会いたい会いたい」が消えないじゃん
Even still, "I miss you, I miss you" just won't disappear
いつだって痛いの痛いの飛んでいかないの
All the pain, all the pain, it won't go away
なんでなんで
Why, tell me, why
寂しさだけ残っちゃってるんだ
The only thing remaining is my loneliness
HOLOLIVE INDONESIA SECOND GENERATION
KUREIJI OLLIE PRESENT
Gemas banget sih~ Kaget kan, gitu?
Your startled face is so cute~
Padahal... ini kan yang kamu nanti-nantikan?
Wasn't this what you were waiting for~?
Bisa bicara sama... oshi...
To be able to talk to your oshi~
Ngapain tuh pencet tombol back?
Hmm, why the frantic button pressing dear?
Jangan-jangan... kamu enggak suka Ollie ngomong langsung...
Don't tell me you actually dislike this kind of interaction~
Ehh~? HP-nya kok dimatiin sih?
Aww why'd you turn off the phone?
Beneran enggak suka ngomong sama Ollie ya...
You really don't want to talk to me, huh~
Keseruannya baru akan dimulai sekarang...
The fun is just about to begin~
ダーリン~
Darling~
存在証明 愛だって 愛だって 吐いたって
Proof of existence, claiming it's love, spewing it's love...
あぁ寝転んゴロンでニャンニャン プリティ プリティ ダイエットDAY
Ah, rolling around, meowing, a pretty, pretty diet day.
曖昧 快楽に 曖昧 快楽に 病み悪化してんだって 愛だ 恋だ 何だってんだ
Vague pleasure, vague pleasure, sickness getting worse, whether it's love or affection, what does it matter?
生命線は 愛だって 愛だ 嘆いたって
The lifeline is love, lamenting that it's love...
あぁああでもない こうでもないな 寂しい 寂しい ナンセンスDAY
Ah, not this, not that either, a lonely, lonely nonsense day.
いっそ 密会ラブに 節操無い 解 LOVE ME 溺れ 奴隷
Might as well go for secret love, an unprincipled solution, LOVE ME, a drowned slave.
踊れ 踊れ 亡霊だ 亡霊だ
Dance, dance, I'm a ghost, a ghost!
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない
Nothing, nothing, I have nothing.
変われない 変われない 私変われない
Can't change, can't change, I can't change.
分からない 分からない 「わかる」 分からない
Don't understand, don't understand, "I get it", don't understand.
はーい 目元以外は 隠して
Okay, hide everything except the eyes!
ダダダダ ダーリン ダーリン はい 冴えない 愛情論で おねだり
Da-da-da-da Darling, Darling! Yes, begging with a dull theory of love.
ダダダダ ダーリン 脳裏 汚 DIRTY 会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダダーリン
Da-da-da-da Darling, in my mind, filthy, DIRTY! Fulfill my urge to see you, Da-Darling!
無い 無い 清純 感情が 行ったり 来たり
None, no pure emotions, coming and going.
無い 無い 純情 感情で ダダダーリン
None, no innocent feelings, Da-Da-Darling!
ダダダダ ダーリン だ 愛だ 喘いだって
Da-da-da-da Darling! It's love, even if I gasp for it.
まあ寝転んゴロンで ニャニャ 食い意地 食い意地 ダイエットDAY
Well, rolling around, meowing, gluttony, gluttony diet day.
もう 精一杯で 罪 暴論 世界で 無理
Already doing my best, sin, reckless arguments, impossible in this world.
病み拓いてんだって 承認 承認 盛大だ
Opening up my darkness, approval, approval, grand scale!
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない
Nothing, nothing, I have nothing.
はしたない はしたない 私 はしたない
Shameless, shameless, I am shameless.
分からない 分からない 「わかる」 分からない
Don't understand, don't understand, "I get it", don't understand.
はーい 自撮りは全部 加工して
Okay, edit all the selfies!
ダダダダ ダーリン FUNNY はい 絶えない 愛情論で 冷めたり
Da-da-da-da Darling, FUNNY! Yes, cooling off with an endless theory of love.
ダダダダ ダーリン 無理 汚 DIRTY 会いたい衝動 止めてよ ダダーリン
Da-da-da-da Darling, impossible, filthy, DIRTY! Stop my urge to see you, Da-Darling!
踊れ 叫べ 踊れ ルラパッパ
Dance, scream, dance, lu-la-pap-pa!
踊れ 唄え 踊れ ルラパッパ
Dance, sing, dance, lu-la-pap-pa!
もう ドッキンドッキンの しんどっきんどッキンの
Already heart-throbbing, painfully heart-throbbing!
はーい 素顔は全部 無くして
Okay, erase your real face entirely!
ダダダダ ダーリン FUNNY どうしようもない 感情論に 笑ったり
Da-da-da-da Darling, FUNNY! Laughing at a helpless emotional theory.
ダダダダ ダーリン 脳裏 汚 DIRTY 会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダダーリン
Da-da-da-da Darling, in my mind, filthy, DIRTY! Fulfill my urge to see you, Da-Darling!
無い 無い 反応 返答を 期待したり
None, expecting non-existent reactions and responses.
無い 無い 妄想 感情で ダダーリン
None, with non-existent delusion feelings, Da-Darling!
無い 無い 純情 感情で ダダダーリン ねぇ駄目？
None, with non-existent pure feelings, Da-Da-Darling, hey, is that no good?
待ち詫びている大通り
Waiting eagerly on the main street
目眩しそうな人混み
In a dizzying crowd
くるり回った昼帯
The daytime spinning round and round
立ち止まってるぼーぼー
Standing still, totally zoned out
しまい切れてない表情
An expression you couldn't quite hide
どこ見てるのぼーぼー
Where are you looking, zoned out?
知らない
I don't know
今なに
What now?
目と目止まった合図
Eyes locking in a signal
ロングのローリーズ
Long Lowrys
「あとでね」
"Talk later"
黒文字
Black text
隠してもムダね
It's useless hiding it
けけけけーたいみしてよ 今から
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone, right now
ねえ 今から
Hey, right now
ねえ いいでしょ
Hey, come on
けーたいみしてよ
Show me your phone
拒んでるの予想通り
Refusing, just as expected
だって賭けたこの試み
After all, this was a gamble
くるり回った昼帯
The daytime spinning round and round
立ち止まっていないで
Don't just stand there
怒ったりしないでよ
Don't get angry with me
I need チュ
I need a kiss
いらない
Don't need it
使い古しの愛も
Worn-out love
言い訳たちも
Or all those excuses
画面じゃなく
Not at the screen
ここ見て
Look right here
取り上げるからね
'Cause I'm gonna take it away
けけけけーたいみしてよ 今から
Sho-sho-sho-show me your phone, right now
ねえ 今から
Hey, right now
ねえ いいでしょ
Hey, come on
けーたいかしてよ 今から
Lend me your phone, right now
けけけけーたいかしてよ 今から
Le-le-le-lend me your phone, right now
ねえ 今すぐ
Hey, right this second
渡しなさい
Hand it over
ねえ いいでしょ
Hey, come on
けーたいみしてよ！
Show me your phone!
Oh! You woke up!
Hi, good morning~! Did you have a good sleep?
Oh, here?
This is Ollie's room!
What was that?
It looks a bit different?
Ehehe~ You found out?
I... prepared this room just for us...
'Cause it's a special room!
Yeah~ I wanted to make our moment as special as possible...
So I worked really hard, and prepared the perfect scenery just for us!
I even transported you here while you were still asleep...
So that you wouldn't get tired~
I just love you so much, and...
I want these feelings to properly reach you~
Huh? What's wrong?
...I'm not like my usual self?
Ehehe~ You're so silly~ I have no idea what you're talking about~
Ah! Wait!
Don't go! Where are you going?
Aww... I can't believe you ran away like that~!
But you were so cute when you were blushing like that~!
指切りげんまん ホラでも吹いたら
Pinky swear, if I tell a lie
針でも何でも 飲ませていただき
Make me swallow a thousand needles or whatever
Monday
It doesn't matter if it's Sunday
鏡よ鏡よ この世で1番
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who in this world is the most...
変わることのない愛をくれるのは誰
Who is the one that gives me unchanging love?
No need to ask cause it's my darling
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのままおサラバするよか
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Still, sometimes my heart gets unfaithful
死んでも治らな治してみせます Baby
Even if it can't be cured in death, I'll show you I can cure it, baby
Yeah I ain't nothin but ya baby
失って始めて気がつくなんて
Realizing what you had only after losing it
そんなダサいこともうしたくないのよ
I don't wanna do something so lame anymore
Goodbye
Oh don't you ever say bye-bye
Eh
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのままおサラバするよか
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおサラバするより
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I choose you over three meals a day
あんたとこのままおサラバするよか
Rather than saying goodbye to you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Still, sometimes my heart gets unfaithful
そんなダサいのはもう要らないのよ Bye-bye
I don't need that corny stuff anymore, bye-bye
I'll always stick wit ya my baby
I'll always stick with ya, my baby
ねぇ
Hey,
アナタには見えない事ばかり アタシは見えている事を 知らないの？
Don't you know there are so many things you can't see, but I can?
背中につけられた 誰かのキスの跡
The trace of someone's kiss left on your back,
一人じゃ買おう訳の無い それも
and those things you'd never buy on your own...
見て見ぬ振りなだけ
I'm just pretending not to notice.
じゃあね
Well then,
笑っちゃうほどにキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it makes you laugh
常時奔放 狂気 短気
Always wild, insane, short-tempered
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if she yells, one look is a knockout blow
洗脳完了 女上手
Brainwashing complete, a clever woman
愛していんのさ 強く愛していんのさ
She loves me, she loves me deeply
ねぇ 精神から全身まで
Hey, from spirit to the whole body,
表面から内面まで
from surface to inside,
脳天から先端まで知りたいの
from crown to toes, I wanna know it all.
それから
And then,
最近聞いた音楽から
from the music you listened to recently
散財した総額まで
to the total amount you spent,
完全把握しないと気が済まないの
if I don't grasp it completely, I won't be satisfied.
とやかく言ったって実際の問題は
No matter what you say, the real issue is
その眼中アタシ何割くらい担ってるか
what percentage of your vision am I taking up?
嗚呼 隠してないで 確信を頂戴
Ah, don't hide it, give me confirmation,
されど黙して語らず
yet you stay silent and say nothing.
バイバイ
Bye-bye.
困っちまうほどにキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's troublesome
容姿端麗 耽美 甘美
Beautiful appearance, aesthetic, sweet
身勝手だって泣くシックな素振り
Even when selfish, her chic manner of crying
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instantly intoxicated, a woman's true blessing
愛しちまうのさ されど愛しちまうのさ
You end up loving her, yet you end up loving her
過去を喰らうほどにポップなエレジー
A pop elegy enough to swallow the past
排気口から香るラーメン
Ramen aroma wafting from the exhaust port
騙し奪われる恋でもいいの
Even a love stolen by deceit is fine
だってこの声は
Because this voice is...
めっちゃくちゃ可愛いでしょ
Super duper cute, right?
笑っちゃうほどにキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it makes you laugh
常時奔放 狂気 短気
Always wild, insane, short-tempered
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if she yells, one look is a knockout blow
洗脳完了 女上手
Brainwashing complete, a clever woman
困っちまうほどにキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's troublesome
容姿端麗 耽美 甘美
Beautiful appearance, aesthetic, sweet
身勝手だって泣くシックな素振り
Even when selfish, her chic manner of crying
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instantly intoxicated, a woman's true blessing
愛していんのさ 強く愛していんのさ
She loves me, she loves me deeply
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the start of the night, bunny girl
誘惑される鼓動に
Enticed by the beating heart
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers with love to bursting conflict
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't convey it to you
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the start of love, bunny girl
誰かを穿って
Seeing through someone
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Holding your clear, serene eyes within
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, step out with a flashy stride
仕事帰りの疲れは 私と このグラスに
Leave your fatigue after work to me and this glass
さあ 自分好みに縋って
Now, cling to what suits your fancy
世間に対する気持ち 私に注いでみない？
Why not pour out your feelings about the world to me?
ありがちなラブソングでも 愛が込められてるの
Even in a cliché love song, love is poured into it
それでも汚れるのね 君を見れば分かるの
Even so, it gets tainted; I can tell just by looking at you
下を向く君の目を 無理矢理剥ごうとはしない
I won't force you to lift your downcast eyes
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸ばべて
So don't make that face, reach out your hand
ほら 夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
Look, it's the start of the night, bunny girl
誘惑される鼓動に
Enticed by the beating heart
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers with love to bursting conflict
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't convey it to you
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the start of love, bunny girl
誰かを穿って
Seeing through someone
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Holding your clear, serene eyes within
君の愛を知った気でハイになっていて 感度去っていて 毎回泣いていてさ
High on feeling like I know your love, numb to sensation, crying every time
それくらいがいいんでしょ
That much is fine, right?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, step out with a flashy stride
君の顔色今では マシになってきてるから
Because your complexion is getting better now
君に委ねるわ Bunny Girl
I'll entrust it to you, bunny girl
私をあげるわ Bunny Girl
I'll give myself to you, bunny girl
誘惑される鼓動に
Enticed by the beating heart
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
Cheers with love to bursting conflict
伝えられてるはず
It should be conveyed to you
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the start of the night, bunny girl
誰かを穿って
Seeing through someone
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Holding your clear, serene eyes within
わっ！
Peekaboo!
見つけた！ずっと探してたんだ！
Found you! I've been looking for you all this time!
かくれんぼしてるなんて教えてくれなかったじゃないか～
You didn't even tell me we were playing hide-and-seek~
やった～！ついにオリーのネオンステージに来てくれたんだね！
Yay~! You finally came to Ollie's neon stage!
どうかな？キラキラしてて可愛いでしょ？
How is it? It's all sparkly and cute, right?
全力で頑張って作ったんだよ～！ネオンもいっぱいあるの！
I worked super hard to make it~! There are so many neon lights too!
君が隠れてる間にね、こっそりお着替えもしちゃったの！
While you were hiding, I secretly changed my outfit too!
オリー、めっちゃ可愛くなったでしょ～？
Ollie became super cute, didn't she~?
へへ～ まだまだ君のために準備したものがたくさんあるんだ～
Hehe~ There are still so many things I prepared for you~
だから、このかくれんぼはもう終わりにしょ～？
So let's end this game of hide-and-seek now, okay~?
えっ？ダメなの？
Huh? You don't want to?
ねえ...
Hey...
Really weird ever since you got here, and...
I just don't understand...
You've been trying to get my attention by liking my posts and commenting on them...
Isn't this what you wanted?
You... You love me, right?
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
Why are you not accepting my feelings? Hehe... You're supposed to be happy, but...
...you're acting so strange...
Eh! W-What? Hey, wait!
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
The way you shut down is killing me!
どんだけ泣いたかわかんないや
I don't know how long I've been crying...
つら 雑魚りっぱ
It hurts, I'm such a pathetic loser.
ぽっかり空いて埋まらないや
There's a gaping hole that won't fill up...
ほしい ラブびったん
I want love, hit me with it.
中々中々っ途な出会いじゃ刺さんないや
A half-baked encounter just doesn't hit home.
やっぱり無理かも ばたんきゅー
Maybe it's impossible after all, I pass out.
げっそりハートが治んないや
My worn-out heart won't heal...
出してよすぐ処方箋
Write me a prescription right now!
サヨナラの棘なんで抜けないの
Why won't this thorn of goodbye come out?
きみの代わりの人形が全然見つからない
I can't find any substitute doll to replace you.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ウブの出棺
Sad Girl Sex, bang bang, farewell to innocence.
好きってどんな思いだったっけな
What did it feel like to love someone again?
誰かと寝ても寂しさが発火
Even sleeping with someone ignites loneliness.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
The way you shut down is killing me!
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ラブの接待
Sad Girl Sex, bang bang, entertaining love.
「きっとまた会える」なんてさ
Saying things like "I'm sure we'll meet again"...
思い出のきみに食い殺されっ子
I'm being devoured by the memory of you.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
The way you shut down is killing me!
ねえ マンガ返してよ
Hey, give me back my manga.
最新話であのキャラ死んじゃったよ
That character died in the latest chapter!
教えてくれたバンド
The band you introduced me to...
メンバーがクスリで捕まっちゃったよ
A member got arrested for drugs!
一緒にいたこと消えないや
The times we spent together won't disappear...
全部が二人だった
Everything was about the two of us.
きっときみは今誰かといるの
You're probably with someone else right now.
あたしだけが課金中
I'm the only one still paying up.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ウブの出棺
Sad Girl Sex, bang bang, farewell to innocence.
嫉妬辛くてエンバッタラー
Jealousy hurts so much, getting embattered.
上書きがしたい どうしてくれるの
I want to overwrite it! What are you going to do?
愛のガチャガチャ 天井はない
Love's gacha machine has no pity ceiling!
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ラブの没収
Sad Girl Sex, bang bang, confiscating love.
ちょっとエゴすぎない？ ほんとさ
Isn't that a bit too selfish? Seriously.
涙の痕に狂気が走った
Madness ran through the tracks of my tears.
愛のガチャガチャ 天井はない
Love's gacha machine has no pity ceiling!
もしもが叶う素敵な世界ならば
If this were a wonderful world where 'what ifs' come true,
きみはサヨナラ取り下げを検討加速しちゃう？
would you accelerate considering taking back your goodbye?
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ウブの出棺
Sad Girl Sex, bang bang, farewell to innocence.
なんでこんな終わってんだろう
Why did it end up like this?
誰かと寝たら埋められるようなレベルの愛だ？
Is it love at a level that can be filled by sleeping with anyone?
そんなんじゃない！
It's nothing like that!
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ラブでぺちゃんこ
Sad Girl Sex, bang bang, crushed by love.
今でも思ってんなわ
Even now, I still think about you.
期待寄りの地獄 もう戻れないの
A hell tilted towards expectation, I can't go back anymore.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
The way you shut down is killing me!
探せ絶頂 続行 だめだめ波あ
Search for climax, continue, no-no wave!
揺らせ絶頂 あせあせ丹
Shake the climax, nervous sweat!
探せ絶頂 続行 だめだめ波あ
Search for climax, continue, no-no wave!
きみの絶頂 効いてんだみょん
Your climax is killing me!
檻の中 あたしの愛猫
Inside the cage, my beloved cat...
おかえりなさい君ににゃお
Welcome home, meow to you.
悪い子ね 汚れたお身体で
What a bad boy, coming back with a dirtied body.
行きはよいで帰りは怖い
Easy to go, but terrifying to return.
愛を知らない 飽き猫さん
A fickle cat who doesn't know love.
間抜けな愛とかそりゃ結構
Foolish love? Well, that's fine.
にらめっこほらバレバレで構想
A staring contest, see, your delusions are obvious.
なんでおしおきだ自己嫌悪
Why a punishment? Self-disgust.
君はあたしだけの愛猫さん
You are my one and only beloved cat.
段々好きになり
Gradually falling more in love...
いない いない 愛して 愛して
Peek-a-boo, love me, love me
ダン ダン 好きになる 好きになる 好きになるねぇ愛して
Step by step, you'll fall for me, fall for me, fall for me, so love me
可愛いね 首輪つけて にゃー
You're so cute, put on a collar, meow
大切に 愛でてあげるにゃー
I'll cherish and adore you, meow
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
Little kitten inside the cage
愛のダンスを踊りましょう
Let's dance the dance of love
喉鳴らし 擦り寄って ほらどうぞ？
Purring and rubbing up against me, here you go
睨めっこ あら甘えん坊さん
Staring contest—my, what a spoiled baby
横を向いてもそれじゃ結構
Even if you look away, that's just fine
君はあたしだけの愛猫ちゃん
You're my one and only beloved cat
ダン ダン 好きになる 好きになる 好きになる 好きになる 愛して 愛して
Step by step, you'll fall for me, fall for me, love me, love me
ダン ダン 好きになる 好きになる 好きになるねぇ愛して
Step by step, you'll fall for me, fall for me, fall for me, so love me
逃げられやしないのバカね
You can't escape, silly
最高の愛をあげるわ 愛して
I'll give you the ultimate love, love me
鎖繋いでだって君は愛猫さん
Chain you up, because you're my beloved cat
Halooo? Kamu di mana?
Hellooo? Where are you?
Ish, keluar, dong!
Ugh, come out already!
Katanya udahan main petak umpetnya?
I thought we were done playing hide and seek?
Kamu ke mana coba...
Geez, where could you be...
Ayo tunjukin dirimu!
Come on, show yourself!
Beneran deh, ngasih kerjaan aja ya kamu...
Seriously, making me search like this, I can't believe you...
Ah!
Ketemu!
Found you!
Jangan ke mana-mana lagi, ya~
Don't go anywhere ever again, okay~?
ほとばしく香る君のその髪が 僕の心を踊らせたんです
The fragrant scent of your hair made my heart dance with joy
靡くだけ 今は それだけで この身屈めますから
Just fluttering, for now that is all it takes to make me bow down
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight ray, darling
堪えきれぬ欲望に任せて
Surrendering to irresistible desire
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight ray, darling
僕に仕える気になったら
If you feel like serving me
願うは三度の絶頂を 胸の中で至る
Wishing for three orgasms to reach deep in my heart
今宵も僕らは繁栄のために愛を放つ
Tonight too, we unleash love for the sake of prosperity
抗いの呟きとは裏腹に 身体は嬉しそうに動いたんです
Contrary to murmurs of resistance, my body moved with joy
この翼に輪を付けるかは 僕ら次第ですから
Whether to put a ring on these wings depends on us
真面目ですかな
Are you being serious?
淫らですかな
Are you being lewd?
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight ray, darling
愛と欲に純白を求めて
Seeking pure white in love and lust
Midnight光線 Darling
Midnight ray, darling
僕を拒む気になっても
Even if you feel like rejecting me
願うは三度の絶頂を 胸の中で至る
Wishing for three orgasms to reach deep in my heart
零れる涙が飽和して 僕はいまに果てる
Overflowing tears reach saturation, and I am about to perish
その溢れた吐息の原因なんだって？
What is the cause of that overflowing sigh?
いったいどこからいったって？
Where on earth did it come from?
ドキドキなんだって？
What is this heart-throbbing?
よろめく恐怖が原因なんだって？
Could staggering fear be the cause?
それでも君ならいいんだって
Even so, if it's you, it's fine
さらに
Furthermore...
願うは三度の絶頂を
Wishing for three orgasms
胸の中で至る
To reach deep in my heart
今宵も僕らは繁栄の...
Tonight too, we are for prosperity's...
ねぇ あたし 愛をもっと吸い愛してよ
Hey, suck up more of my love and love me back
願うは三度の絶頂を
Wishing for a triple climax
胸の中で至る
Reaching deep inside my chest
零れる涙が飽和して
Overflowing tears reach saturation
僕はいまに果てる
And I am about to expire
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know it all
君がひとり泣いてるの 知ってるよ
I know that you're crying all alone
ビクンビクン怯えてさ
Trembling and terrified
声も出せないんだわ
Unable to even make a sound
正直にいっちゃいよ
Just be honest and spit it out
バレてるんだしいっちゃいよ
It's totally obvious, so go on
効いてんの？ 恥ずかしい？
Is it working? Feeling embarrassed?
みんな隠しているだけ
Everyone's just keeping it hidden
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know it all
君がひとり涙してるの 知ってるよ
I know that you're shedding tears all alone
グスングスン凹んでさ
Sniffling and feeling down
弱い人だからいいんじゃない？
You're weak, so isn't that totally fine?
朝が来るまで一緒コース
We're together all night long until morning comes
もっと泣いたってなんだって
Cry even more, do whatever you like
受け止めてあげる
I'll accept every bit of you
もう我慢しないでいっぱい出してね
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out
お願い 君が欲しいの
Please, I want you
慰めさせて シェイク シェイク
Let me comfort you, shake shake
愛の才能で 泣いてくれなきゃ
With my talent for love, if you don't cry for me
枯れてしまう 濡れていたいねえ いいでしょ？
I'll wither away, I wanna stay wet, hey, isn't that okay?
舐めとって 飲み干したいんだ た た たってば
I wanna lick it off and drink it all up, I said!
お願い 君が欲しいの
Please, I want you
頼り散らして シック ラブ
Rely on me all you want, sick love
なんで最高ね 活けてくれなきゃ
Why is it so awesome? If you don't revive me
君の痛い 感じていたいねえ いいでしょ？
I wanna feel your pain, hey, isn't that okay?
吸いとって 救いたいんだ た た たってば
I wanna suck it out and save you, I said!
見たい 見たい 見たい... 君の中
I wanna see, I wanna see, I wanna see... inside of you
見たい 見たい 見たい...
I wanna see, I wanna see, I wanna see...
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know it all
君がひとり悔しがってんの 知ってるよ
I know that you're feeling frustrated all alone
ズキュンズキュン高まるよ
My heart beats faster and faster
君を襲うことをやめない
I won't stop preying on you
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know it all
君はできる子 知ってるよ
I know that you're a capable child
辛いときは弱いくらいでちょうどいい
When times are tough, being a bit weak is just fine
あたしそれでも好きだよ
I love you all the same
お願い 君が欲しいの
Please, I want you
名前を呼ぶのよ いったって
Call my name out loud
会いに参上 君はひとりだ
I'm here to meet you, you're all alone
だから歌う ひとりじゃない もういいでしょ？
That's why I sing, you're not alone, isn't that enough?
ソロプレイはおしまいなんだ た た たってば
Solo play is over now, I said!
君が病めるときも あたし側にいるわ
In sickness, I will be right by your side
いつも見守っているわ
I'm always watching over you
そうよ 怖くないのよ
That's right, there's nothing to fear
お願い 君が欲しいの
Please, I want you
慰めさせて シェイク シェイク
Let me comfort you, shake shake
愛の才能で 泣いてくれなきゃ
With my talent for love, if you don't cry for me
枯れてしまう 濡れていたいねえ いいでしょ？
I'll wither away, I wanna stay wet, hey, isn't that okay?
舐めとって 飲み干したいんだ た た たってば
I wanna lick it off and drink it all up, I said!
お願い 君が欲しいの
Please, I want you
頼り散らして シック ラブ
Rely on me all you want, sick love
なんで最高ね 分けてくれなきゃ
Why is it so awesome? If you don't share with me
君の痛い 感じていたい 塞いでたい
I wanna feel your pain, wanna block it out
吸いとって 救いたいんだ た た たってば
I wanna suck it out and save you, I said!
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know it all
君がひとり 涙してるの 知ってるよ
I know that you're shedding tears all alone
グスングスン 凹んでさ
Sniffling and feeling down
弱い人だからいいんじゃない？
You're weak, so isn't that totally fine?
朝が来るまで一緒コース
We're together all night long until morning comes
もっと泣いたって
Cry even more
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept every bit of you no matter how many times
もう我慢しないで出したったったってば
Don't hold back anymore, let it out, I said!
ふぅ！
Phew!
Akhirnya selesai juga!
Finally done tying you up!
Sekarang kamu nggak bisa kabur lagi~
Now you can't run away anymore~
Jadi duduk manis aja ya~
So just sit tight like a good boy, okay~?
Beneran deh, kamu bikin kerjaan aja ya!
Seriously, you really made me work up a sweat!
Sampe aku harus cari kamu, kejar kamu~
To the point I had to look for you and chase you down~
Yaa, yang penting kita sekarang bertemu kembali~
Well, the important thing is we're finally together again~
Sekarang kita bisa nikmatin waktu kita deh berdua~
Now we can finally enjoy our time together, just the two of us~
Wo! Sini... こっちを見ろよ...
Hey! Look over here...
Nah, gitu dong~ いい子いい子〜
There you go~ Good boy, good boy~
Karena kamu sudah duduk manis kek gini, waktunya untuk aku perliatin ke kamu hasil kerja aku selama ini!
Now that you're sitting nice and tight like this, it's time for me to show you what I've been working on all this time!
Lihat deh! これを見てください！
Take a look at this!
今回も誕生日グッズが出まーす！
We're releasing birthday goods this time too!
1つずつ紹介していきますね！
I'll introduce them one by one!
Yeah, there will also be a birthday goods for this year, so I'll be introducing it to you guys one by one, okay?
Yeah, there will also be birthday goods for this year! So I'll be introducing them to you guys one by one, okay?
はい！じゃあ、1つ目のアイテムはこちら！
Alright! Then, the first item is this!
Wow! It's a wide rubber mat! Isn't this so cute?
working, wherever you're...
...gaming, you'll always remember me!
The theme, it kind of looks like a Yandere, doesn't it? But I'm not a Yandere!
I'm just your girlfriend.
Yeah, it's wide, slightly large size, rubber mat, recommended for everyday use!
And the illustration is by 花澤明先生!
And the illustration is by Hanazawa Aki-sensei!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you so much!
Okay! Then, the next item will be... こちら!
Okay! Then, the next item will be... this!
Wow! It's a pillow! Isn't this so cute?
クッションだよ。ダイカットクッション。
It's a cushion. A die-cut cushion.
So that when you're sleeping, you'll remember me, you'll dream of me!
This... it looks so fluffy! So you guys better get it for a good night's sleep!
Alright! And followed by... こちら!
Alright! And followed by... this!
It's a ring necklace!
Well, it's a ring. If it doesn't fit your size, then you can just wear it as a necklace. Isn't that really cool?
そう、これはね、指輪。でも、えっと、サイズが合ってないなら、
So, this is a ring. But, um, if the size doesn't fit,
ネックレスでも使えることができます！
you can also use it as a necklace!
It's so cute! So make sure that when you go out, you wear this!
So that whenever you go grocery shopping, no other girls out there will be hitting on you!
はい! And then, we also have... こちら!
Alright! And then, we also have... this!
It's a mug! Isn't it so cute? I really like the design!
So, not only when you're working, or gaming, or grocery shopping,
or sleeping, but even when you're drinking, you think of me!
And of course, not forgetting... こちら!
And of course, not forgetting... this!
Situational voices in three languages!
In 日本語, in Bahasa Indonesia, and English!
In Japanese, Bahasa Indonesia, and English!
Wow! As always, さすが me! さすが me!
Wow! As always, as expected of me! As expected of me!
はい! そして最後にフルセットを購入いただいた方には、
Alright! And lastly, for those who purchase the full set,
数量限定で直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードが付いてきます！
a limited-quantity autographed instant photo-style card is included!
And for those of you guys who buy the full set, there will be a limited edition postcard with my message and my sign!
Jadi, buat yang beli full set-nya, bakal dapet postcard dari Ollie, ada message, ada tanda tangannya juga!
So, for those who buy the full set, you'll get a postcard from Ollie with a message and signature too!
Yes!
次は、通常版は箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードが付いてきます！
Next, the standard version comes with a foil-stamped replica autograph instant photo-style card!
For those of you who buy like the normal version, you guys can also get a postcard with my sign and message!
Yang beli versi biasa juga akan dapet postcard yang ada message dan sign-nya!
Those who buy the regular version will also get a postcard with my message and signature!
Phew... Okay, that is all! That was a mouthful, wasn't it?
But you'll buy my merch, won't you?
That's what I like to hear!
Phew...
I wish I could spend more time with you, but unfortunately, our time is limited.
Damn.
But I have one last thing that I'd like to gift to you. So I hope you'll pay attention and wait for me, okay? Don't go anywhere!
こっちを向いて
Look this way.
声を上げて
Raise your voice.
私を見て
Look at me.
私だけを見て
Look only at me.
ゾッとした表情が可愛いね
So cute when you're terrified.
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want every bit of your body.
Love it? ナニにラリって
Love it? What are you high on?
愛 High 可哀想ね
High on love, how pathetic.
君は悪い子なの
You're a naughty boy.
どの娘がお好きで？
Which girl do you prefer?
散々に色目がお上手で
So good at making eyes at everyone.
頭湧き
My head is swimming.
君に踊らされちゃって
Danced around by you,
アタシは狂う
I'm going insane.
What is love it?
君の血肉まで
Deep into your flesh,
骨の髄まで
right down to the marrow,
挿れて空っぽになる
filling you until you become empty...
愛のパペット
...a puppet of love.
胸が苦しいね
My chest feels tight,
息が詰まるのね
and I can't catch my breath.
それが恋と教えてあげる
I'll teach you that this is what love is.
あはは
Ahaha!
虚ろな声で
With a hollow voice,
ほら囀いて
come on, whisper to me.
いい子ね 首輪付けた
Good boy, now wearing a collar.
君は Love it
You are love it.
イカれちゃったの？
Have you gone crazy?
Noね 恋は盲目ね
No, love is just blind.
したいよね
You want to, don't you?
してあげるわ
I'll do it for you.
逝って？
Die for me?
あはは
Ahaha!
濡れて君の赤い生液
Soaked in your red blood,
溺れるまで
until I drown in it.
愚かね 愚かね まぬけな顔して
How foolish, how foolish, making such a silly face.
君は悪い子なのだ
You really are a bad child.
痛いのが好きでさ
Since you like pain so much...
あら お口はチャックで
Oh, zip your mouth shut.
何？何？
What? What?
性に踊らされちゃう
Dancing to your own desires.
君を喰らう
I shall devour you.
血肉 骨の髄まで
Flesh and blood, to the very marrow of your bones...
しゃぶりつくせば もう空っぽのパペット
If I suck you dry, you're just an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね
Your chest feels heavy, doesn't it?
息が詰まるのね
You're choking up, aren't you?
それが恋と教えてあげる
Let me teach you that this is what love is.
君はピエロね
You're just a clown, aren't you?
愛を囁いて
Whispering sweet love...
人間の形した君はラブ？
Shaped like a human, are you love?
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone completely mad, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is truly blind, isn't it?
死にたいのね してあげるわ
You want to die, don't you? I'll do it for you.
報い切れない 汚れに溺れるまで
Until you drown in unatonable impurity...
痛い痛いの飛んでけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until you stop breathing.
報い切れない 汚れに溺れるまで
Until you drown in unatonable impurity...
痛い痛いの飛んでけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away, until you stop breathing.
Thank you so much for coming to watch the 3D Birthday Live!
How was it? Did you feel my love?
Oh, look at that! A specially prepared bedroom! Cute, isn't it?
There's a bed, a sofa, Udin, and...
...I don't know if you noticed, but there was a display photo of the people I cherish the most in there!
I think the neon stage was really cool, too!
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs sitting around.
And, well, those are there to help me watch you from afar~
Cool, right?
Ah, but come to think of it, I really did drag you around the stages, huh?
Um, how are you? Do you feel sick? Are you okay?
I'm a bit worried, but I think it shouldn't affect you too much, since I carried you while you were still sleeping...
Huh? What? No, nothing! I didn't say anything!
Um, speaking of you, you kept running and hiding away from me!
Naughty, naughty! Tsk, tsk!
You always leave comments and like every post I make, so I thought you'd like it if I came to visit!
I didn't think it would actually surprise you that much!
I think maybe it was because you were too surprised when I suddenly appeared in front of you?
But just so you know, I worked really hard just for you!
I practiced my singing, I sang a lot, and changed my outfits so many times...
And I wonder if my feelings reached you...
It obviously did, right?
Also, at the end, I finally managed to catch you!
That's what you hoped for, right?
I mean, 'cause you were running away from me!
Because you love me a lot, obviously you were expecting it too, right?
Hehe, period!
Anyway, for those of you who are still watching, thank you by the way, I have an announcement!
Ollie will be featured in SO87's song 'Love Me Back', with the music video!
It's going to be so cool, so keep an eye out, okay?
It's just so exciting, isn't it?
If you ever feel the need to feel my love again...
...then don't hesitate and please come back to watch the 3D Birthday Live again, okay?
I'll always be here waiting for you!
Anyways, bye-bye!
Otsucrazy~!
Crazyになるほど恋しているZOMBIE
A zombie who's so in love it's driving her crazy
君のハートを狙い撃ち
I'm taking aim at your heart!
腐敗した愛？ ううん、フレッシュだよ！
Rotten love? Nope, it's fresh!
キミのことが好きすぎて死にそう
I love you so much I feel like I'm gonna die!
（あ、もう死んでたわ！）
(Ah, I'm already dead!)
墓場の中からアイラブユー
Sending you "I love you" from inside the grave!
生き返るほどキミが好き
I love you enough to come back to life!
脳みそ溶けちゃう！ ラブラブゾンビ！
My brain is melting! Lovey-dovey zombie!
ガブッと噛みつく情熱で
With a passion that bites right in,
キミの心をジャックする！
I'll hijack your heart!
腐っても鯛？ ううん、ゾンビだよ！
"Even rotten, a bream"? Nope, a zombie!
腐敗しても愛は腐らない！
Even if I decay, my love won't spoil!
永遠にキミを愛してる！
I'll love you for all eternity!
Crazyになるほど恋しているZOMBIE
A zombie who's so in love it's driving her crazy